and what is that you have behind there collapsed collapsed
а что это у тебя сзади там такое
Yes the wall fell the
обваленные обваленная Да стена упала
pipes burned out you see everything And what
трубы прогорели видишь всё А что
happened Well everything is rotten pipes And why do
случилось Ну всё прогнили трубы А что ты
n't you do the
не сделаешь
repairs I welded them for starters And these are the
ремонт я я заварил для начально А это
pipes that come from the housing and communal services wait for
трубы которые идут от ЖКХ подожди поди
replacements And how long have you had this one a
замены А сколько уже у тебя вот эта
month and you live in this
месяц и ты живёшь в этом
Hello Hello and please tell me
Привет Здравствуйте а раскажите
what is the Glory of Ukraine And I didn't
пожалуйста в чём Слава Украины А я не
say Glory of Ukraine And I know that you didn't
говорил Слава Украины А я знаю что вы не
say Glory of Ukraine is it quality I
говорили Слава Украины это качествен я
just don't live in Ukraine I am a
это я просто не живу в Украине Я
citizen of the Russian Federation I live in
гражданин Российской Федерации живу в
Europe And yes I just support Ukraine I
Европе А да просто поддерживаю Украину я
can say in MM What is the Glory of
могу сказать в ММ В чём Слава Европы А
Europe And you will say What is the glory of Russia
вы скажете В чём слава России
no wait What is the Glory of Europe Glory of Europe Europe is
нет подождите В чём Слава Европа Слава
rich Russia is poor those What is the glory of Russia
Европы Европа богатая Россия нищая те В
everyone is rich Europe
чём слава России всем богата Европа
why then why
почему тогда а почему а почему
then Europe is fed with gas from Russia it does
тогда Европа это питается газом от
n't feed because Europe
России так не питается пото что Европа
was rich it bought gas from poor Russia
была богатая она покупала у нищей России
now Europe buys gas from America
газ теперь Европа покупает у Америки газ
And from
А у
Russia Why if Europe is rich
России А почему она если Европа богата
why  she bought gas from Russia
почему она покупала у ни России газ
Why because you can buy it from these for next to nothing Yes
Почему потому что у этих можно за
Okay And if you're
бесценно купить было да Хорошо А если вы
not like for Ukraine Why do you have this
типа не за Украину Почему у вас это
chevron of Ukraine I'm for Ukraine I'm saying I'm a
шеврон украи Я за Украину Я говорю я сам
citizen of Russia myself I live in Europe well
гражданин России живу в Европе хорошо В
What is Glory to Ukraine I don't know what Glory to
чём Слава Украине Я не знаю в чём Слава
Ukraine I don't know what Glory and why do
Украине Я не знаю в чём Слава а почему у
you have a chevron on it because I
вас шеврон на ней потому что я
support Ukraine giving it to
поддерживаю то чтобы Украина давала
Russia here in the Kursk region by the way
России вот в Курской области мне кстати
I can't do it yeah look
я ну не получается да смотри
from Ero dol on drones and they brought me from the
из еро дол на дроны и мне привезли с
Kursk region
Курской области
Present so it's clear it's
Презент так это понятно это любой номер
called any number you can
называется любой номер можно
bring We can also bring
привести Мы также можем привести с
only numbers from Ukraine Look you see And
Украины лько номеров Смотри видишь А в
what look I told you Glory to my
чём смотри я тебе сказал Слава моей
Europe we are a rich country here I live in
Европы мы богатая страна вот я живу в
Germany
Германии
Europe is a union of countries Look I'm in
по Европа это союз стран Смотри я в
Germany You are a citizen of which country a
Германии Ты гражданин какой страны
citizen of Russia and
гражданин ро и
Germany Yeah and why are you hiding right away and
германи Ага а что ты скрываешься сразу а
so that you don't take a screenshot don't send it
чтоб ты не сделал скриншот не отправил
Nowhere And what are you afraid of right away no no
Никуда А что ты боишься сразу нет нет
just why
просто ну зачем
Adi everything is okay let's do it I won't do it
Ади всё ладно давай я делать не буду
take your hands away I see
забери руки я вижу отстав
I'm behind I'm still behind my hands Show your hands
я всё отстав руки Покажи руки
and not show Show Because you
а не показать Покажи Потому что ты
want I left those And you And you it turns out And
хочешь Я оставил те А ты А ты получается
you it turns out you're afraid yes come on not you're
А ты получается боишься да давай не ты
hiding behind a cap and so what Slava ra And you And
скрываешься а так в чём Слава ра А ты А
you it turns out wait wait and you And you're a
ты получается подожди стой а ты А ты
citizen of Russia you say and you and and you're
гражданин России говоришь и ты и и
hiding behind a cap Yes I have I
кепкой скрываешься Да у меня У меня
just have a mom in Rostov with a dad I don't want
просто мама в Ростове с папой Я не хочу
them to have problems But that's
чтобы у них были проблемы А вот оно в
what the matter is and if you
чём дело а е а если
ask no need you'll be shorter simple
спроси не надо ты будешь короче простой
we'll find you then and you Yes you'll get
мы тебя тогда найдём и тебя Да ты
tired of
заебёшь
looking for my dear come on like this explain it to
искать родной давай так вот объясни по
Come on ke come on come on come on
Давай ке нука ну-ка давай-ка
poorly alive And I live I'm not poorly living If
бедно жив А я живу я не бедно живу Если
I lived poorly I have nothing to eat now even
бы я бедно жил у меня сейчас кушать даже
at home you have nothing to eat damn what did
Дома нечего у тебя нечего жрать блин что
I not do
я не
you look in the freezer what did mom
вил ты заглядывал морозилку чтом мама
say anyway there isn't any and there's no dairy
говорила по-любому нету и молочки нету
this is definitely in Russia
это однозначно в Росси
show me on camera
меня показать на камеру
And you you have nothing you have everything I have
Аты у тебя ниче нету тебя меня всё есть
no you have zero nothing come on yes yes yes yes
нету у тебя ноль ничего нету давай да да
I do this Show show your
да да я это Покажи покажи свои
products seriously And you Show yours come on show the
продукты серьёзно А ты Покажи свой давай
products I'll show your face I answer
покажешь продукты покажу лицо отвечаю
No no on the contrary Show yours I'll show yours you
Нет нет наоборот Покажешь свой покажу
answer hide breakdown you answer
свой отвечаешь скрывай срыва отвечаешь
hide
скрываешь
I already took your screenshots anyway do you
я в любом случае скриншоты уже твои
think I
сделал ты думаешь портам
burned the ports Well listen well you didn't send it so that
ли спалил Ну слушай ну ты не выслать
mom doesn't have
чтобы мамки не было
problems tell my mom definitely wo
проблем пове у моей мамки проблем точно
n't have problems so show me the products now come on
не будет так показывай теперь продукты
What products are at home yes
Какие продукты дома лежат да
And you have a birthday you don't want to
А у тебя День Рождения ты не хочешь
see Which one Which one Vlad
посмотреть У какого У какого У Влада
Ermakov Well the size I know that Vlad
Ермакова Ну размера Я знаю что у Влада
Ermakov's birthday is on the 2nd Yes that's
Ермакова 2 первого числа будет День
right he'll be 19 and
рождения Да это да это прально 19 лет
19 Yes not for
будет а 19 Да
myself
себе
9 So wait is it 19 or 29 did you get off
9 Так подожди стоит 19 или 29 лся с тебя
29 you Rub what 19 is that's the
29 ты Потри какой 19 такой так в том-то
thing that I think me Explain to me what
и дело что я думаю меня Объясни мне что
kind of city is mache
такое за город маче
gorsk what did you
горск ты что
screenshot Yes I've been locked up for a long time Yes that's
заскринил Да я тебя уже давно закрити Да
not it  I'll tell you Vlad Ermakov so And we
не так Я же скажу Влад Ермаков так А мы
now let's now we
сейчас давай сечас мы
pos I know this one
пос Я знаю эту
through which you just purely Come on
через которую ты просто чисто Давай
shows show the products I'll show you
показы показывай продукты покажу
go yeah yeah I let it be
пошл да Дада я пускай
Who are you that I'd show you the
будет Кто ты такой чтобы я тебе
products because my mom
продукты поэтому потому что мне мамка
told me yeah that because of the sanctions there are no
говорила да что изза санкции сейчас не
eggs in the
стало яиц в
stores now
магазинах
A yeah Well okay okay okay okay okay
А да Ну ладно ну
let's move
так Ладно давай
on I became interested yeah where do I work Tell
дальше Мне интересно стало
me
Дада где я работаю Расскажи мне
ses
сес
Come on let's show the products
Давай давай показывай
No with the products Tell me
продукты Нет с продуктами Расскажи мне
where I work show the products that's where I work that's
где я работаю показывай продукты та где
with the products show the products
я работаю та с продуктами показывай
Yes where the products are where I
продукты Да где продукты там где я
work you see you your information
работаю видишь ты у тебя информация твоя
will turn out to be false so
окажется
So you're still an athlete youth
так Так ты ещё спортсмен юношеский
category have and
разряд имеешь да
play So in what in what now fight now
играешь Так в чём в чём сечас сеча сечас
So in what at least
Так в чём хоть
so hockey defender Oh handsome Yes oh
так хоккей защитник Ай красивый Да
Germanovich so Ermakov Vladislav
ай германович так Ермаков Владислав
Germanovich yes And now Name the address of registration
германович да А теперь Назови адрес
registration now we
прописки сейчас мы
are checking you checking me
тебя пробиваю пробива меня
completely Yeah now now
полностью Угу
now  and in hockey In which one with a sword or with a
сейчас а в хоккее В каком с мечом или с
puck Calm down Which one with a sword Something like this
шайбой Успокойся какой с мечом
Yeah, just a second Ermakov
Ага сейчас секундочку Ермаков
o Come on, darling, drink me up completely,
о Давай родной полностью меня пропивай
so phone +79 53 309 28 30 Yeah, right
так телефон +79 53 309 28 30 Ага се
now they'll give you a test call
сейчас тебе тестовый звоночек сделают
Come on, right now, so let's do it You try
Давай давай сейчас так давай сде Ты
harder, right now,
главное получше старайся
so here's the Murmansk region, the city of
так так вот Мурманская область город
Monchegorsk, Leningradskaya embankment, house
Мончегорск набережная Ленинградская дом
10, apartment 33
10 квартира 33
Yeah Well, let's do it I'm waiting for you as a guest
Ага Ну так давай я жду в госте тебя
now, now, so now our specialist will call you Yeah, he'll say hello
сейчас сейчас Так сейчас тебе позвонит
So now I'm
Так сейчас я вот номер
sending the number, so there's come on Let's read
отправляю так есть давай Давай читаем
what else there is So come on, come on Uh-
что ещё есть
huh
Угу
about the federal
о федеральных
bailiffs, some kind of debt had Yes, where are
приставов должок какой-то имел
you from
Да ты
Abkhazia
откуда се Абхазия
Abkhazia my father is from Amra, I'm
Абхазия у меня отец из амры родом я
half ACU And who are you by
наполовину ацу А ты кто по
nationality,
национальности
Russian, Russian in Abkhazia What are you
русский русский в Абхазии Что там
doing there, I'm relaxing, and you're relaxing, that you're not from
делаешь отдыхаю а отдыхаешь что ты не из
Abkhazia You're from
Абхазии Ты из
Russia Why Where did you come from in
России Почему Откуда ты приехал в
Abkhazia
Абхазию
Russia I ask where do you live in
России я и спрашиваю где ты живёшь в
Russia where are you from
России откуда ты из
Russia in
России в
Abkhazia I am now in Abkhazia Tell me
Абхазии яня сейчас в Абхазии Скажи
where from What city in Russia did you
откуда Из какого города России ты
come to
приехал в
Abkhazia from and
Абхазию а
Yekaterinburg all according to Zhirinovsky Now I
Екатеринбург всё по Жириновский Теперь я
understand
понимаю
Zhirinovsky He just spoke about the residents of the Urals in exactly the
жирика Он просто о жителей Урала
same way Well, he
Жириновский очень как раз так отзывался
said that they have a specific
Ну и говорил что у них специфический
level of intelligence
уровень интеллекта
Well, I dont
Ну не
know exactly I cant
знаю точно не могу тебе
tell you where exactly in Abkhazia you are
сказать где именно в Абхазии ты
now Im a su Yes I do
сейчас я су Да я
nt Im
нет
fine in Sukhum Yes you are in Sukhum now
Я хорошо в Сухум Да ты в сухуме сейчас
yes yes I understood how the weather is in Sukhum
да да понял как там в сухуме погода
yes its warm normal how much the
да тепло нормально сколько
temperature is exactly 15 I understood And how long have
температура именно 15 понял А как давно
you been in
ты в
Sukhum How long has it been a year Almost a year then are
сухуме Сколько уже год на Почти год то
you on vacation for a year or are you already
ты отдыхаешь год или ты там уже
working there me your own business
работаешь меня свой бизнес
Ask wha there is a little bit and what kind of business is a
Проси вха немножко есть а что за бизнес
cafe cafe cafe and in Abkhazia a cafe
каф кафе кафе и в Абхазии кафе
made Well yes
сделал Ну да
nuva And where is business better in Abkhazia
нува А где лучше идёт бизнес в в Абхазии
or in
или в
Yekaterinburg of course
Екатеринбурге конечно
better Shes small
получше Она же малень
Yes I understood Listen, what do you think Why is
Да понял Слушай как ты считаешь Почему
Russia in
Россия во
Well I think everything is visible here well who is who
Ну я думаю тут всё
Ukraine is to blame
Украина
why Well, it all started back in the
почему Ну так это всё началось-то ещё с
nineties So what exactly
девяностых годов так А что именно
started how to say That's
началось как те сказать
all in the nineties Yes, and the Maidan was
Вот это всё в девяностом Да а Майдан был
in the nineties or In the nineties
в десто вром или В девяносто
What started that way You said that it
чем в начался так ты сказал что началось
all started in the nineties That's what
всё с девяностых Вот мне
interests me I say Maidan started in the
интересно я говорю Майдан в
fourteenth year You said that back in the nineties
четырнадцатом году начался ты сказал что
That's what started in the nineties
ещ с де вот что с девяностых началось
Explain Well, preparation That's all That's what in the
объясни Ну подготовка Вот это всё С
nineties Ukraine was preparing for the
какого девяностого года готовилась к
Maidan Since the
майдану
fifth somewhere like that
Украина с пятого где-то вот так
ninety-fourth year Yeah So, how
девяносто четвёртый год Угу Так а как
exactly In ninety-five ninety-
именно В девяносто пятом девяносто
four they started preparing
четвёртом начали готовить
the Maidan Well, if you tell this it's a
Майдан Ну если это рассказывать это
very long story It lasts for about three hours
очень надолго на тянется Часа на три на
Well, at least approximately I'm
Ну хотя бы хотя бы примерно мне
interested That is, they started cultivating
интересно то есть начали выращивать
Yanukovych or what to prepare for the Maidan
Януковича или что для Майдана готовить
Well, presidents Yes, Crimea That's all it went that what
Ну президентов Да Крым Вот это всё пошло
kind of Maidan again come on Maidan in
что какой Майдан ещё раз давай Майдан в
Kyiv what have they been doing since the nineties  fourth
Киеве что делали с девяносто четвёртого
year in Kyiv Yes, how they prepared
года в Киеве Да как готовили
Maidan Well, weapons, money, a billion
Майдан Ну оружие деньги миллиард
dollars, I think, were reimbursed for Maidan
долларов по-моему на Майдан было
since 1994
возмещен с девяносто четвёртого года
yes
да
yes And where will you read that since
да А где вы такое прочитаете что с
1994, a billion
девяносто четвёртого года миллиард
dollars for
долларов на
Maidan I say the preparation was since
Майдан Я говорю подготовка была с де че
1994 That is, I understand correctly, and
года То есть я правильно понимаю а
Maidan was in 2014 That is, it turns out that the
Майдан был в 2014 То есть получается
Revolution was 20 years ago yes
Голи 20 лет да
yes And how many billions
да И сколько миллиардов
were spent Well, I cant tell you the exact amount,
пустили Ну точную сумму тебе не могу
no one will tell us Well,
сказать никто нам не скажет Ну
approximately according to your
приблизительно по вашим
estimates Well, I dont know exactly Well, you also
оценкам Ну не знаю точно Ну вы же тоже
said some
сказали какие-то
billions Well, for 1 billion purely for Maidan, the
миллиарды Ну на 1 млрд чисто на Майдан
SPU prepared this, this E plus, I
СПУ подготовку вот этого это Е плюс я
think there are 500 billion, he says 500 billion were given to
думаю там 500 млр же говорит 500 млрд на
Maidan Well,
Майдан
there are many things that
дали Ну там много что
say Do you know that they
говорит Ты знаешь что на Майдане
handed out pierced tangerines and
раздавали э наколотые мандарины и
oranges on Maidan,
апельсины
no Do you know where they were brought from, from
нет А знаешь откуда их везли с
Abkhazia Perhaps from
Абхазии Возможно с
Abkhazia And how do you know that a billion
Абхазии А откуда ты знаешь что Миллиард
dollars were spent on Maidan
на Майдан пустили долларов
Everyone is saying this Open any website directly
это все говорят Это впрямую любой сайт
official everything is written there where is the
открой официальный там всё написано где
official website I want to
официальный сайт Хочу
open even this how the
открыть даже это как его
hell is it a woman
блин баба-то
forgot her last
забыл
name she said it herself Yaka
фамилия она сама говорила Яка
woman Yes I
баба Да фамилию
forgot her last name remember on n on ends with en on n
забыла вспоминай на н на кончается
starts with end ends the end
эн на н начинается на end кончается the
no ending Valentina
end нет окончание Валентина
Zendov yes
зендов да
No seriously I'm saying Liliya Kurent Well
Нет серьёзно говорю Лилия курент Ну
just type just a Lili Liliya
просто набери просто а Лили Лилия
Kurent No no no Type Just in Google
курент Нет нет не Набери Просто в Гугле
on end I'll type now What does en have to do with it Well
на end сейчас наберу
now well an American
Причём тут эн Ну сейчас ну американская
woman on
баба на
en Mila Cleveland American she's not
эн Мила Кливленд Американ она не
American
американская
she's from Germany I don't remember where from
она Германии не помню откуда с
Germany So what's on Well just type
Германии Так какая на Ну просто набери
Just type
Просто набери
[music]
[музыка]
Who said who And how much
Кто сказал кто А сколько
money did she spend on creating Maidan That's how you
потратила денег на создание Майдана Во
write it
напиши
now I wonder how on
сечас Интересно как на
end damn I forgot her last name
end блин Забыл фамилию её
Well approximately at least the first
Ну приблизительно хотя бы первая
letter Yes I don't remember honestly I
буква Да не помню честно говорю я те
said the final letters approximately not even
сказал конечные буквы примерно даже не
exactly 90% or something
точно 90% что
now one more time now now on Google Come on come on now I'll
сейчас ещ раз сейчас сейчас на Гугли
ask with the assistant's voice I
может спрошу
wonder
Интересно
like this Okay Google please tell me
так Окей Google скажи пожалуйста меня
here a
тут
Russian asks what some
спрашивает россиянин что какая-то
woman with a last name
женщина на с фамилией которая
ending in ND said that a
заканчивается на НД говорила что на
billion dollars were allocated for Maidan who was it
Майдан выделили миллиард долларов кто
and where did this information
это был и откуда вообще эта информация
come from I answer this nonsense was invented by Russian
отвечаю эту муть придумали русские
propagandists Skabeeva and Simonyan
пропагандисты скабеева и симоньян такое
only
могут рассказывать только
Russian women who don't understand anything can say such things in
россиянки не понимающие Ничего в
life this is a Ukrainian voice
жизни так это это украинский голосовой
assistant You ask Google this is Google I
помощник Ты у Гугла спроси это Google Я
said Oh Google
сказал Ой Google ещё
again Okay Google please tell me Who
раз Окей Google скажи пожалуйста Кто
said that
говорил что
1 billion was allocated for Maidan you froze do you
на Майдан выделили 1 млрд ты завис
hear me froze froze why is
слышишь меня завис завис
their roulette froze Well
завис что у них зависает рулетка Ну
damn
блин
Ivanka this is a Ukrainian voice search Ask
Иванка это украинский голосов пощи
Google Hello Hello Where are you from
Гугла Привет Здравствуйте Ты откуда
Streamer Streamer got caught I am from Russia
Стример Стример попался Я с России
stream and how do you communicate Well so in general how do
стриме а чем общаешься Ну так вообще как
people think about when it will all end
люди думают о том когда всё закончится
Nobody knows when it will end
Никто не знает когда закончится
absolutely not well as some
абсолютно не ну как какие-то
assumptions there was hope that
предположения была была надежда что
Trump will come now in short and force
сейчас придёт Трамп короче и заставит
Ukraine to sign a capitulation Well damn You
Украину подписать капитуляцию Ну блин
see I am from Rostov there don't
Видишь я вообще из Росто там же не
look I am not I am from  Rostov like yes I'm
смотри я я не Я из Ростова типа да я
trolling like I'm breeding them I
троллю типа я развожу их Я сейчас в
live in Germany now So my mother was German my
Германии живу Так у меня мама немка была
father was Russian like I've been living in Germany for 18
отец русский типа я живу в Германии 18
years I dressed like I
лет это я оделся так типа я украинцев
communicate with Ukrainians like we wo
общаюсь с ними типа что мы уже Германия
n't support them anymore Germany and so
не будем это поддерживать их и так
on I troll a little So you're for
дальше немножко троллю Так ты ты за
Russia then Well how do I support Russia I'm
Россию тоь Ну как я топлю за Россию я
not for Russia at all not for Germany I'm
вообще не за Россию не за Германию я
like for the
типа за
truth I'm purely like that No well what do you
правду Я чисто так
think Well It should be
Не ну сам как думаешь Ну Оно же должно
when it ends Well look here in
же когда кончи Ну смотри у нас в
Germany it's here Honestly I really do
Германии тут оно Честно говоря мне очень
n't like it because they included
не нравится потому что включили
all our defense plants in this production
в эти производство все оборонные заводы
so I have a department somewhere 14 km from me
наши так вот у меня где-то 14 км от меня
there
там есть отделение
they stupidly do it
это они тупо короче делают
for
для
Ukraine without interruption and the trains go somewhere
Укра бесперебойно и эшелоны идут куда-то
there to Poland and then
туда на Польшу а дальше
Damn so now at the present time the
Блин так сейчас же на нынешнее время
capacities that were great
мощностях которые были велико
domestically and now they are almost
отечественно и сейчас они же там чуть ли
three times smaller there yeah well look
не в три раза меньше же да ну так смотри
at the fact that the capacity The fact is that in
в том что мощность Дело в том что в
Russia we still have old Soviet ones Yes that's the
России у нас ещё старые советские Да вот
same thing  BT You talk about machine tools, I
так же само БТ Ты про станки говори я и
talk about the Armed Forces. Yes, but look, the thing is
про ВС говор Да а тут смотри тут дело в
that the
том что очень
Bundestag allocated a lot of funding
сильно Бундестаг выделил финансирование
and our gunsmiths
и наши оружейники они пролабирование
wanted to help Ukraine prolapsed, and then
хотели помогать Украине да а потом вот
these oligarchs who own weapons factories,
эти олигархи которые оружейны заводами
there is this Rosenfeld and there is
владеют там этот есть розенфельд и есть
this Schwartz cop,
это Шварц коп
they financed Schwartz cop - that's the one that
они профинансировал Шварц коп - это
makes shampoos and this is shampoo. Look,
которая шампуни есть и шампу это Смотри
this is a surname in general, Schwartz cop means black
это фамилия вообще Шварц коп это чёрная
head
голова
in translation, if so, this is a very
в переводе если так это очень
common surname for us, like in
распространённая у нас фамилия типа в
this is shampoo for brunettes and shampoos in Germany.
это в Германии шампуня для брюнета и
There are also
шампуни Есть тоже да
such ones, and it turns out that they lobby for the
такие и получается Они пролоббировать
Bundestag to allocate money.
чтобы Бундестаг выделил выделили бабки
Before the New Year, they are simply
ещё Перед Новым годом Сейчас просто в
working three shifts now. I have a friend who
три смены работают Вот у меня знакомый
also works on this armored vehicle. He doesn't
есть тоже работает на этой бронке Он не
say that they sign something that they
говорит они что-то подписывают что они
cannot disclose what is there.
не могут разглашать что там да
No, in fact, Germany is
Не ну сейчас по факту Германия она е
now. It
сейчас Что
produces everything, it produces everything,
производит всё производит всё производит
and missiles, look, these Tauras. They
и ракеты вот эти таурас
say that Taus, I am
смотри Нам типа говорят что Таус я
specifically  specifically if by nodes then Well with
именно конкретно если по узлам то Ну с
leopards in my opinion no longer so the thing is that
леопардами по-моему уже нет так дело в
look with tanks There is a different
том что смотри с танками Там по-другому
thing that at first they wanted to give
дело в том что сначала хотели давать
tanks and then they saw that tanks make no
танки а потом посмотрели что танки не
sense to give tanks in this war
имеют смысла давать танки в этой войне
they are practically not effective both from
они практически не действуют что с
Ukraine and from the war of Daro drones and
Украины что с война Дронов Даро и
therefore Yes they are in short because it makes no
поэтому Да они короче потому что не
sense to give this leopard for millions
имеет смысла этот леопард за миллионы
in short everything was redistributed
короче давать всё пере распределились У
We have these German instructors They
нас вот эти инструктора немецкие Они они
are in Ukraine definitely definitely I
есть в Украине однозначно однозначно Я
know a friend Yes who e goes there
знаю знакомого Да который э ездит туда
he goes there for six months there a month in Germany six months
он полгода там месяц в Германии полгода
there a month in Germany they are in all the hot
там месяц в Германии они на всех горячих
spots this is where Where does he go there
точках это откуда Откуда он ездит туда
from Hamburg from Hamburg not you
из Гамбурга из Гамбурга не ты
say six months there six months in Ukraine
говоришь полгода там полгода в Украине
he is in Ukraine for six months he is an instructor that is
он в Украине полгода он инструктором то
officially ours there are no Germans
есть официально наших там нету немцев
officially Yes in reality there are
официально Да в реальности их там вот
all these And you, you have one citizenship or
эти все А ты у тебя гражданство одно или
you are a citizen of a citizen of a I because I
ты д гражданства д я из-за того что я 18
lived there for 18 years it turns out and I already had
лет там прожил получается и у меня уже
somewhere about 9 years ago no not Ukraine I have
где-то 9 лет назад было не не Украина у
Russia and  Russia and Germany I'm
меня Россия и Россия и Германия Я же
telling you I'm from Krasnodar And now for
говорю я из Краснодара родо А сейчас за
whom in the majority as
кого большинстве как
if well look I told you I'm from
бы ну смотри я же тебе рассказал Я из
Krasnodar I'm from live in Germany I'm
Краснодара родом живу в Германии это я
trolling well That is to say you're completely
троллю а ну То бишь ты целиком полностью
for Russia I'm yea I first they
за Россию полу я да я сначала им они
see me they shout Glory to Ukraine I
меня видят кричат Слава Украине я там
set up a VPN there and I say yes I'm from Germany
VPN поставил и я говорю да я из Германии
nothing from Russia we won't help you anymore
ни тало из рни гово вам больше не будем
And they're
помогать И они
like well that's harsh of course Well so I
такие ну это жёстко конечно Ну так я
troll as best I can No well God forbid only to
троллю как могу Не ну дай Бог только
stay on our territory later
чтобы на нашей территории потом остаться
When they start debriefing Well
Когда у них там разбор полётов начнётся
yes Well I have two citizenships if anything I'm
Ну да Так у меня ж два гражданство если
there and there yes The main thing is on time No no well
что я туда туда да Главное вовремя Да не
everything God forbid Wait And what
ну всё дай Бог Подожди А ты из какого
city are you from what city are you from I'm from the
города ты из какого города я я с
Kemerovo region Kuzbass from Siberia myself
Кемеровской области кузбас с Сибири сам
Yes Kuzbass Novokuznetsk
Да кузбас Новокузнецк
Kemerovo What is written on you You don't see
Кемерова Какой у тебя же написано Ты же
me it's not written no And what city Well
ви меня не не написано нет А какой город
from there of course of course Kuzne I have my
Ну оттуда конечно ну конечно кузне у
grandfather was a miner in
меня у меня у меня дед был шахтёром в
Novokuznetsk a miner  respect Yes so what and
Новокузнецке шахтёром респект Да так что
there
а там
sl with Metallurgov and
сл с Металлургов и
ul I looked What is this news Yes what the
ул Я смотрел Что там это новости Да что
governor said that the problem with the
губернатор заявил что проблема с
coal industry is very big yes
Угольной отраслью Очень большая да
now Keme
сейчас Кеме
VS dig everything sell where they sell
ВС копают всё продают та куда продают
stopped selling earlier here to
перестали продавать раньше сюда в
Germany
Германию
they pushed you see how you see for the air
толкали видишь как видиш для эфира
now you can talk a lot then
сейчас можно много договорить потом
stay I just briefly say that there are no
остаться я те просто коротко ска что с
problems with aluminum in Novokuznetsk
алюминием проблем нет в Новокузнецке
one site of the aluminum plant
одна площадка алюминиевого завода
closed the other is functioning
закрылась другая функционирует
fully
полноценно
where they sell now Why do we
куда продают тепер Зачем нам просм
mortals need to know where they
смертным знать куда это
sell it the main consumer will always
продают основной потребитель всегда
be China This was it will be it will
будет Китай Это и было это будет это
remain not on China we are on China we have so much
оста не на Китай мы на Китай мы столько
coal not in I will not be surprised that they bring it to India
угля не во я не удивлюсь что в Индию
and everything else So listen in
возят и всё остальное Так что слушай в
terms of where to sell here you can
плане того что Куда продавать тут можно
not worry only
не париться только
guess from Kemerovo to India coal is carried to yourself
гадать из кемеро в Индию уголь воз себе
imagine So
представ связа Так
what am I telling you about the railway
чем я тебе вообще говорю железнодорожные
line do you think you saw how much the
линия ты думаешь ты видел сколько
railway carries coal to India And you
железной дорого в Индию вести угля А ты
Okay let's put it differently And you
Ладно давай по-другому А ты про Монголию
know a lot about Mongolia what is happening in  Mongolia
много знаешь что творится в Монголии
now, for example, on And when was the last time
сейчас допустим на А когда последний раз
you read anything about Mongolia in the news
ты в новостях вообще про Монголию что-то
Well, for example, approximately I am
читал Ну вот к примеру примерно Я на
also exiled there through Mongolia, they have already
тоже ссылают там через Монголию уже
thrown and that's it and to India through
кинули и всё и воз и в Индию через
Mongolia, the
Монголию
railway is carried by ships, by
железная дорога кораблями возят
ships through Mongolia Yes, I am speaking figuratively to you, it
кораблями через Монголию Да я тебе
is aluminum, I will tell you for sure, aluminum
е алюминий я тебе точно скажу алюминий
through ports and by ships And where is
через порты и кораблями А куда
it, wait in Kemerovo, from Kemerovo to the
он подожди в Кемерово от Кемерова до
nearest port, it is cargo shipments, you
ближайшего порта это грузок отгрузок ты
are telling us, cargo shipments, this is the
рассказываешь у нас грузок отгрузок это
same thing, the coal itself will be
же нес дело что само куз уголь куда-то
brought somewhere, this is also clear, there is a
привезут это же понятно дело идёт
party, packaging, they are
тусовка расфасовка в всё
bringing everything I just see that there I will not
везут Просто я виж что там не буду
say And then you never know Well, not me I just
говорить А то мало ли Ну не я Я просто
saw what they wrote Yes, what about the
видел что писали Да что задолженность по
wage arrears of 4 months,
зарплатам 4 месяца
no You are talking about now about the mine that
нет Ты про сейчас про шахту которая
was literally the news a few
новость была буквально сколько несколько
days ago Yes, and a few days a month
дней назад Да и несколько дней месяца
ago, from my acquaintances who
назад было из моих знакомых кто на
work in the mines,
шахтах работах ни у кого задолженности
no one had any arrears, everyone received them on time, I dont know where
не было все получили вовремя не знаю
this came from  news about the service And what is that
откуда эта новость о слу А что это у
you have behind there collapsed
тебя сзади там такое
collapsed even the Price has fallen the
обваленные обваленная даже Цена упала
pipes have burned out You see what and what
трубы прогорели Видишь что а что
happened Well, everything is rotten pipes And why do
случилось Ну всё прогнили трубы А что ты
n't you do the
не сделаешь
repairs I welded it for starters And these are the
ремонт я я заварил для начально А это
pipes that come from the housing and communal services Wait,
трубы которые идут от ЖКХ Подожди
wait for a replacement And how long have you had this one for a
подожди замены А сколько уже у тебя вот
month
такая месяц
and you've been living in it for a month and nothing has been
и ты живёшь в этом месяц а ниче мне
welded for me all the way to the tap the pipes are not mine
заварили все до крана трубы это не мои
to the tap the pipes are the housing and communal services we're still waiting for a replacement
до крана трубы это ЖКХ всё ждём замены
why should I bother paying my
зачем я буду заморачиваться платить свои
money to change To change an entire floor of my
бабки менять Менять целый этаж своего
flight so that the housing and communal services should have my taps
пролёта чтобы что ЖКХ должны краны мои
whole my pipes in the apartment are whole this and what
целые мои трубы в квартире целые это а
year is this apartment straight so cut I'm just wondering not
года пря так рез просто интересно не
for Russia it's not just what year is the
же за Россию то не просто какого года
apartment Well, you're supporting Russia It's just that
квартира Ну ты же за Россию топишь
we have Krasnodar Wait, wait,
Просто у нас краснода Подожди подожди
answer my question You know
ответь мне на мой вопрос Ты же знаешь
all the nuances In Russia, how is all this done
все нюансы В России как это всё делается
undercut Come on, well, my dad and
подреза Брось вообще ну у меня батя с
mom You're a troll Supposedly you're for Russia and you're
мамо Ты же троли Якобы ты за Россию и ты
now undercutting as if you know how in
сейчас подреза как будто ты зна как в
ROSI is going to change in Krasnodar with mom there is
РОСИ дется с менят в Краснодаре с мам
nothing like that there are
ти там не такого там сам
sets yourself right now you are writing right now on the
сеты же сейчас пишешь же сейчас на
stream with how many people are watching you now Yes,
стриме с сколько тебя сейчас смотрят Да
not on the stream what are you and don't tell me
не на стриме что ты да не рассказывай
how many people are watching you now I have no idea
сколько тебя сейчас смотрим Я понятия не
I'm not on the
имею Я не на
stream Explain to me how it happens
стриме Объясни мне как так получается
what year did you have
какого года у тебя
this I was born he was probably already And
этот Я родился он уже был наверно А тебе
how
сколько
old are you anyway young I'm 25
лет вообще молодой Мне 25
I have
у меня
stubble the hair on my face started growing
щетина волосы на лице начали расти
earlier than me that's all Listen I'm 43
раньше чем я вот и всё Слушай мне 43
you're really
тебе реально
25 Well you see the
25 Ну ты ты видишь
beard put the camera a little further away from yourself
бороду камеру чуть-чуть дальше от себя
Maybe it's a camera from close
поставить Может это камера с близка
So I'm telling you I have no beard I'm generally
Так я тебе говорю я без бороды Я вообще
Kitten I
Котёночек
answer you in the sense I'll shave and all this is
тебе отвечаю смысле я поброюсь и всё это
just
просто
nicotine uh a bad lifestyle and such a voice
никотин э-э плохой образ жизни и голос
and all And so 2 m and weighing 100 kg Well
такой и вся А так 2 м и весом 100 кг Ну
what I
то что я
agree Well you see That's what I'm talking about
согласен Ну вот видишь Я же про что и
telling you the addresses and
говорю что рассказать тебе адреса
I'm talking about that it
ися я про что и говорю что оно оно
really was a dialogue by the way on
действительно диалог получился кстати в
the air they only put in A on  youtube there is a
эфире вкладывают только А на юбе есть
channel where with Yes I'm not a YouTuber what are you talking about me
канал где с Да я не ютубер что ты ко мне
yes you you already called me you say that you are
да ты ты меня уже назвал ты говоришь что
not this you will post this
ты не это ты же будешь это выкладывать
where to watch it I don't post you are
где смотреть-то я не выкладываю ты
some kind of damn some kind of
вообще какой-то блин какой-то
abnormal you just said Well what
ненормальный ты сейчас сказал Ну то что
I agree Well you said it was a joke
я согласен Ну вот ты сказал это прикол
really a joke well no well in the sense
такой реально прикол ну не ну в смысле
you just said what sog in fact
ты сейчас сказал то что сог по факту
wait you in fact it turns out I'm
подожди ты по факту получается я я
joking I have the most Irony And you have such a
стебусь у меня самая Ирония А ты такой
brazen meaning Insulting me and saying that it's
смысл нагло Оскорбляешь меня и говоришь
normal Wait mo clarify
о том что это нормально Подожди мо уточ
You are now smoking on the toilet
Ты сейчас на унитазе
yes I'm sitting on the toilet lid smoking Well
да на крышке унитаза сижу курю Ну а
why ah where why do they all sleep I'm
почему а а куда зачем у меня спят Все я
sitting quietly And there is a balcony somewhere to
сижу тихонечко А есть балкон где-то
smoke rooms it's cold winter outside
покурить комнаты холодно зима на улице
what are you from Russia You should know
ты что ты же с России Ты же должен знать
that in Siberia z and you Wait And
что в Сибири з а у тебя Подожди А у тебя
someone else
дома кто-то ещё
lives at your house of course a cat and a dog Yeah I get it it's brutal
живёт конечно кошка и собака Ага понял
you probably stink like that You are
жесть у тебя наверное так воняет Ты же
you right now  you understand that I'm bending you over right now
ты же сейчас понимаешь что я сейчас тебя
like you're trying to
через нагибаю как ты пытаешься меня
bend me over well in fact Yes Listen but really
нагнуть ну по факту Да Слушай а реально
can you show me what
Ты можешь показать как у тебя выглядит
this bathroom looks like at
вот эта ванная комната что как как что у
yours what how how what my bathroom looks like
меня выглядит ванная
here you see well this is the top and the
комната вот ты же видишь ну это верх а
bathtub itself you don't have any washbasins yes
сама ванна умывальных есть у тебя нету
yes the toilet it's a toilet it's a problem even the
нету да унитаз он унитаз он бед ту даже
same
же
hands writing on my Telegram right now axis
руки пись на мий Telegram прям зараз ось
VN and
ВН а
while this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scarg ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos I don't show people sometimes I don't
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we can write operational links
того щоб ми ма оперативный звязок
right now and while there in Telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okrim videos there are also interesting and useful
окрим вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry with you trimati
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
fast operational links
постный оперативный звязок
independently in that chi will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
subscribe A
подпишись A